Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Photographs PC0062
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photographs, Series 1
  - Negatives without prints
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Hoover Tower construction, with worker, negative (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Hoover Tower construction, with worker, negative (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Hoover Tower construction, with worker, negative (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Hoover Tower construction, with worker, negative (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Hoover Tower construction, with three men posing, negative (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Museum, negative (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Palm Drive, Oval, Front of Quad, negative (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified construction scene, negative (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Unidentified construction scene, negative (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Prints
    - Green Library, 1980 (4 color prints) (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - History Corner, 1980, (3 color prints) (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Jordan Hall, entrance details, (10 color prints) (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Jordan Hall, entrance details, (9 color prints) (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Hoover Tower interior, circa 1970, print (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Arch, Memorial Church, 1976, print (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Physiology Building (01-460/420), 1976, print (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Outdoor sculpture not at Stanford (photos, postcards, illustrations) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Outdoor sculpture - brochures, magazines, clippings, notes, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Negatives (35mm) of Lathrop carriage house, summer 1992 (now demolished) and of The Bridge, summer 1992 [ACCN 93-006] (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Oversize photographs
    - View of Quad from rear showing Church steeple and Memorial Arch (pre 1906) (Box 10)
    - Mitchell Earth Sciences building and University Press building, 1980s (Box 10)
    - Lomita Drive in front of Museum, 1980s (Box 10)
    - Serra Street near Sequoia Hall, looking toward Quad, 1980s (Box 10)
    - Post '06 quake repair work on Quad building (Box 10)
    - Front view of Quad, pre '06, probably taken from new library dome (Box 10)
    - Museum and Chemistry building, probably pre '06 (Box 10)
    - Sheep grazing in front of Quad, post '06 (Box 10)
    - Registration scene outside Memorial Auditorium, circa 1950s - 2 shots (Box 10)
    - Aerial photographs (16) of the campus, university lands, and neighboring communities, 1958-1962 and undated. Includes one published view of Palo Alto by The National Press. (Box 11)
    - Color image of the model for Science and Engineering Quad, circa 1996 (Box 11)
    - Encina Gym interior, negatives, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Museum, original light fixtures (prints and negatives), circa 1996; and miscellaneous views of the interior prior to reconstruction, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Museum, second floor ceiling prior to reconstruction, circa 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Old Quad restoration (projects 320 & 260), slides by Joel Simon, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Historical American Buildings Survey (HABS No. CA-2613) of the west wing of Green Library (1919 building): set of 63 prints; photos taken by David De Vries, Dec. 1994 (Box 13)
    - Historical American Buildings Survey (HABS No. CA-2613): incomplete duplicate set of prints (Box 14)
    - SEQ: Electrical Engineering Building, color photos taken Aug. 27, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - SEQ: Electrical Engineering Building, color photos taken Sept. 25, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - SEQ: Electrical Engineering Building, color photos taken Oct. 28, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - SEQ: Electrical Engineering Building, color photos taken Nov. 25, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - SEQ: Electrical Engineering Building, color photos taken Nov. 23, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - SEQ: Electrical Engineering Building, color photos taken Dec. 21, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - SEQ: Connective element, color photos taken Oct. 28 and Nov. 25, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - SEQ: Connective element, color photos taken Nov. 23, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - SEQ: Connective element, color photos taken Dec. 21, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - SEQ: McCullough Annex, color photos taken Sept. 25, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - SEQ: McCullough Annex, color photos taken Oct. 28, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - SEQ: McCullough Annex, color photos taken Nov. 25, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - SEQ: McCullough Annex, color photos taken Nov. 23, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - SEQ: McCullough Annex, color photos taken Dec. 21, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - SEQ: two undated images (printed from scanned photos) (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Additional Photographs (Negatives), 1963-1970; Accession ARCH-2001-305
  - Volume 1, 1961-1965 (Box 1)
    - 1963 May 16: Primary road system; land uses; medical school - hospital; utility systems; General plant improvements; faculty club and others
    - Circa 1964: Primary Road System, Press Expansion and Publications Buildings, SLAC
    - Circa 1964: Fine Arts Site [1962], Proposed New Mineral Sciences Building, Campus Drive Extended, and others
    - 1965 January: Biology Buildings
    - 1965 April: Phase III Master Plan (aerial); Maples Pavilion; and others
    - 1965 Sept. 9: Menlo Park, Proposed Office Building, Sand Hill Road, Frat Group III, On-Call Quarters, Hoover Tower
    - 1965 Sept. 9: Hoover Tower, On-Call Quarters, and Others
    - 1965 Sept. 16: Public Fac. For the Wall Street Journal, Wheatley Jacobson Inc., RandD Lab for Fairchild Semiconductor, Underground Electrical System--P.A., and Others
    - 1965 Sept. 16: Hoover Tower, Portola Valley, Menlo Park, On-Call Quarters, and Others
    - 1965 Oct. 2: Hoover Tower, Elementary Schools, Encina, Hewlett-Packard Co., SLAC, and Others
    - 1965 Nov. 2: Hoover Tower, and Others
    - 1965 Nov. 18: Electrical Sys., Water Sys., Steam, Hopkins Marine Station, and Others
    - 1965 Nov. 18: Roscoe Maples Pavilion, Student Housing, Hoover Tower, Wilbur Masters Residence, Electrical System, and Others
    - 1965 Dec. 16: Lease Renewals, Space Engineering Bldg., Roscoe Maples Pavilion, Hopkins Marine Station
    - 1965 Dec. 16: Medical School, Wilbur Hall Faculty Master's Residence, Hoover Tower, Electrical System of P.A., and Others
    - 1965 Dec. 16: Athletic Facilities and Others
  - Volume 2, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
    - 1966 Jan. 19: Frat Group III, Cowell, Hoover Tower, Athletic Facilities, Master Lab Plan
    - 1966 Jan 19: Proposed Leases, LM 5 Area, Art Building, Varian, Sanitary System, Land Use, Roads
    - 1966 Feb. 17: Master Lab Plan
    - 1966 Feb. 17: Land Use, Conversion for Engineering, Elect. Sys. of P.A., P.A. Auto Center, and Others
    - 1966 March 17: Fire and Police Station, Bubble Chamber Housing, and Others
    - 1966 March 17: Primary Road System, High Energy Physics Lab, Fire and Police Station, Union Remodeling, and Others
    - 1966 March 17: High Energy Physics Lab, Undergrad Lib., and Others
    - 1966 April 19: Margaret Jacks, Robert S. Moore House, Bechtel Inter. Center
    - 1966 April 19: Robert S. Moore House, Stanford Shopping Center, Margaret Jacks House, and Others
    - 1966 April 21: Land Use, Space Engineering Bldg., Stanford Industrial Park, and Others
    - 1966 May 19: Lomita Mall, Earth Sciences Bldg., HP Lab, and Others
    - 1966 May 22: University Lands, Bechtel Inter. Center, Roads
    - 1966 May 31: Professional Admin Area, SLAC, Land Use Plan-Central Campus, and Others
    - 1966 May: University Lands, Income, Earth Sciences, Bechtel Inter. Center
    - 1966 June: Earth Sciences Building, and Others
    - 1966 June: Lomita Mall, Earth Sciences Building, and Others
    - 1966 June: HP Lab, SLAC, and Others
    - 1966 July 2: Encina West Wing renovation; Fire and Police facility; Varian basement addition
    - 1966 July: Fire and Police facility; Animal Farm for Medical School; Joseph Magnin store; Syntex Interim Facility
    - 1966 July: Hewlett Packard; High Energy Physics Lab; SLAC Central Services; and others
    - 1966 July: Smith Klein and French Laboratories; High Energy Physics Lab; Encina West Wing renovation; central campus map
    - 1966 July: Hewlett Packard; Syntex Interim Facility; Varian basement addition; and others
    - 1966 July: Syntex Interim Facility; Smith Klein and French Laboratories; School of Medicine
    - 1966 July: Fire and Police facility; Dept. of Biochemistry renovation; SLAC Central Services; High Energy Physics Lab; central campus map
    - 1966 July: Fire and Police facility; Encina West Wing renovation; School of Medicine
    - 1966 Sept.: Clock Tower (photos); High Energy Physics Lab; Medical School model; SLAC landscape design
    - 1966 Sept.: SLAC landscape design; High Energy Physics Lab
    - 1966 Sept.: High Energy Physics Lab model and drawings
    - 1966 Sept.: Assorted studies for unnamed project; Addison Wesley; 1962 Master Plan map
    - 1966 Sept.: Assorted studies for unnamed project; Smith Klein and French Laboratories; Addison Wesley
    - 1966 Sept. 21: Junipero Serra Freeway; Stanford Industrial Park; Smith Kline and French Laboratories; and others
    - 1966 Sept. 19: Foothills gas system; Medical School Computer Facility; High Energy Physics Lab Extension; and others
    - 1966 Sept.: High Energy Physics Lab Extension; Smith Kline and French Laboratories; and others
    - 1966 Oct.: Escondido Village -- models
    - 1966 Oct.: Medical School Computer Facility
    - 1966 Oct.: Smith Kline and French Laboratories; Escondido Village
    - 1966 Oct.: Smith Kline and French Laboratories; Medical School Computer Facility; Feasibility Study for Site 14; Addison Wesley
    - 1966 Oct.: Smith Kline and French Laboratories; Medical School Computer Facility; Feasibility Study for Site 14; Addison Wesley
    - 1966 Nov.: SLAC; Library Quad Master Plan Study; High Energy Physics Lab extension
    - 1966 Nov.: Plaque from first gymnasium/track oval; Palo Alto Square; Stanford Industrial Park (Calif. Avenue); and others
    - 1966 Nov.: Stanford Industrial Park (Calif. Avenue); High Energy Physics Lab extension; College Terrace
    - 1966 Dec.: Residential Site Development Plan; Master Plan for Stanford
    - 1967 Jan.: High Energy Physics Lab extension; SLAC; Watkins Johnson Co. dining and seminar facility
    - 1967 Jan.: High Energy Physics Lab extension; 651 Welch Road; Stanford Units Instant Space; Computation Center
    - 1967 Jan.: SLAC, 851 Welch Road
    - 1967 Jan.: High Energy Physics Lab Extension, Dining and Seminar Facility for Watkins Johnson Co.
    - 1967 Jan.: SLAC, Industrial Park, Watkins Johnson Co. Dining and Seminar Facility
    - 1967 Jan. 19: 851 Welch Road, Watkins Johnson Co., Professional Administrative Area SU
    - 1967 Feb.: Encina Hall Renovation, Research Lab
    - 1967 Feb.: Stanford Shopping Center, San Francisquito Creek, Research Lab, SLAC, Elementary School, and others
    - 1967 March 16: Stanford Construction Program [orig. negs missing; reshot Aug. 1968]
    - 1967 April: Pine Hall, SLAC, and others
    - 1967 April: Professional Commercial Center, Space Engineering Building, Central Campus Master Landscape Plan
    - 1967 April: Old Bookstore, SLAC, Space Engineering Building
    - 1967 May 18: Lomita Mall, Hopkins Marine Station
    - 1967 May 18: Branner, Stanford Industrial Park, Professional Commercial Center, Facility for Applied Technology Inc.
    - 1967 June 15: Biology Building, Stanford Shopping Center
    - 1967 June 15: SLAC, Jordan Hall, Encina Hall, Medical School Dept. of Radiology
    - 1967 June 15: Medical School Dept. of Radiology, Encina Hall, Hoover Tower Renovations
    - 1967 July 5: Radio Field Sites and others
    - 1967 July 19: Modernization of High Energy Physics Lab, Building 110, Inner Quad Renovations
    - 1967 July 19: Air Conditioning Units, Chilled Water Systems, Biology Building, Lomita Mall and others
    - 1967 July 19: Animal Farm for Medical School, Research Lab, Stanford Shopping Center, and others
    - 1967 Sept. 11: Eastman Kodak, SLAC, Overhead Power Lines to Radio Field Sites
    - 1967 Sept. 21: HEPL, Stanford Industrial Park, Existing Air Conditioning Units on Campus, Incorporated areas on Stanford lands in San Mateo County
    - 1967 Sept. 21: HEPL, Chilled Water Distribution Systems, Incorporated areas on Stanford lands in San Mateo County, Earth Sciences Building
    - 1967 Oct. 16: Pedestrian and Bicycle Routes, Off Street Parking, Intent of Land Uses, Copies of photographs
    - 1967 Oct. 16: Intent of Land Uses, Bank Building on Page Mill Road
    - 1967 Oct. 19: Bank Building on Page Mill Road, Air Conditioning and Chilled Water Systems, Bank Building and Office Tower Palo Alto, and others
    - 1967 Nov.: Medical School Dept. of Radiology
    - 1967 Nov.: Off Street Parking, Feasibility Study for Site 14, and others
    - 1967 Nov.: Aerial photos of campus, Site Study for Institute of Comparative Medicine and Veterinary Science, Site for New Chemistry Building, and others
    - 1967 Nov.: Oak Creek Apartments, Aerial Views of Stanford Lands, Medical School Dept. of Radiology
    - 1967 Nov.: Law School model, Stanford Industrial Park, and others
    - 1967 Nov.: Law School model (part of larger campus model), and others
    - 1967 Dec.: Oak Creek Apartments, Sand Hill Improvement Project, New Law School facilities, Development Plan for Chemistry quad
    - 1967 Dec.: Model for Oak Creek Apartments, New Law School facilities, Site Study for Institute of Comparative Medicine and Veterinary Science, Stanford Industrial Park
    - 1968 Jan. 8: Chilled water system, air conditioning, Alfred Electronics and Others
    - 1968 Jan. 17: Roll C: Jordan Hall, steam, water, and Others
    - 1968 Jan. 17: Roll D, sheet 1: HEPL, Meyer Library, temporary student housing, parking, circulation, sewers and Others
    - 1968 Jan. 17: Roll D, sheet 2: Escondido, HEPL, Jordan Hall
    - 1968 Jan. 17: Roll E: Electrical, Water, Sewer
    - 1968 Feb. 5: Sculpture location, Control Data Corporation
    - 1968 Feb. 15: Sheet 1: Control Data Corporation, Alfred Electronics, and Others
    - 1968 Mar. 11: Roll F, sheet 1: Meyer Library, Bank of California (Page Mill Rd office), Industrial Park development maps, and Others
    - 1968 Mar. 11: Roll F, sheet 2: HEPL and Others
    - 1968 Mar. 11: Roll G: HEPL, assorted utilities
    - 1968 April: Roll A: SLAC, Navy ROTC addition, Physical Plant Department
    - 1968 April: Roll B: Meyer Library, Main Library and Others
    - 1968 May 16: Temporary building, School Of Med., and Others
    - 1968 May 14: Proposed Office Building, 1000 Welch Road
    - 1968 June 3: Architectural models: Law School and Hopkins
    - 1968 June 3: New chemistry facilities, Hopkins, Library master plan
    - 1968 June 10: Proposed store front, site locations, computer science building, Escondido Village Increment 4, and Others
    - 1968 June 13: Escondido Village Increment 4; new Law School facilities; Site location, Music Dept.; Stanford Industrial Park; Hopkins Marine Station
    - 1968 Aug. 8: Oak Creek Apartments and Others
    - 1968 Aug. 15: Lomita Mall, Animal Research Center
    - 1968 August: Medical Center master plan, Centrex building, Stanford Memorial Church, and Others
    - 1968 Sept. 30: Architectural model of Athletic Facilities
    - 1968 Sept. 30: Athletic facilities, engineering buildings
    - 1968 Sept.: HEPL, SLAC, and Others
    - 1968 Sept.: Alza Corporation, Hewlett Packard, Sand Hill Improvement Project, Memorial Church
    - 1968 Oct.: Law School, Central Food Services, Alza Corporation, HP Building 16
    - 1968 Oct.: Modernization of HEPL, Athletic Facilities, Escondido Village corp yard
    - 1968 Oct. 17: SUL Master Plan, Central Food Services and Others
    - 1968 Oct. 17: HP Building 16, Engineering Bldgs 530, 540 Remodel, and others
    - 1968 Nov.: Escondido Village Increment 4 - drawings and model, SLAC welding shop
    - 1968 Nov. 4: Master Plan for Athletic Facilities, Dermatology Expansion, United California Bank, Museum, Stanford Industrial Park
    - 1968 Nov. 4: Syntex, Central Food Services, Major Facilities 5-yr Forecast, and Others
    - 1968 Nov. 4: Escondido Village model, Stanford Shopping Center, and others
    - 1968 Nov. 4: Optics Technology, Escondido Village Increment 4, and others
    - 1968 Nov. 21: Optics Technology
    - 1968 Nov. 21: Earth Sciences Building, SUL Master Plan
    - 1968 Nov. 21: Stanford Shopping Center, Sand Hill Improvement Project, Escondido Village Increment 4, Syntex Production Building, older photographs of Stanford University
    - 1968 Nov/Dec.: Syntex
    - 1968 Dec.: Intent of Land Uses, Tentative 2-year Building Design Starts, Building Projects under Construction, Tentative Map Stanford Industrial Park
    - 1968 Dec. 9: Utility systems, Parking, Circulation, Major Facilities Program 5 Year Plan
    - 1968 Dec. 9: Utility systems
  - Volume 3, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - 1969 Jan. 13: EV Increment 4, Dermatology Extension, Central Food Services
    - 1969 Jan. 13: Professional Commercial Center, Stanford Industrial Park, United California Bank, Wells Fargo Bank
    - 1969 Jan/Feb.: 5-Year Plan
    - 1969 Jan/Feb.: Utilities, Parking
    - 1969 Jan/Feb.: Circulation, Parking
    - 1969 Feb. 3: 900 Welch Road Office Building, SUMC "Surge" Building Site, and others
    - 1969 Feb.: Parking
    - 1969 Feb.: Utilities, Parking, Research and Development in Teaching Site Location, Library Quad Master Plan, and others
    - 1969 Feb.: Parking [positive images]
    - 1969 Feb.: Utilities [positive images]
    - 1969 Mar. 11: Utilities, Parking
    - 1969 Mar. 24: Project Plans for Landscape Function and Tree Planting on State Highway; and others
    - 1969 Mar. 24: Nixon School, Welch Road Dental Center, and others
    - 1969 April 7: Campus townhouses
    - 1969 April 8: Dental Clinic, Welch Rd; Industrial Park
    - 1969 April 28: Assorted: student housing in mobile homes; industrial park
    - 1969 May 12: Assorted: student housing in mobile homes; land use; industrial park
    - 1969 May 13: Industrial park buildings
    - 1969 May: Assorted: SLAC, HEPL
    - 1969 June 3: Assorted: music building, computer science building
    - 1969 June 13: Assorted: research and development center, education; music building; Escondido Village
    - 1969 June 13: Center for Advanced Studies in Behavioral Sciences
    - 1969 July 30: Industrial Park
    - 1969 Aug. 25: Pediatric Clinic
    - 1969 Aug. 25: three drawings
    - 1969 Sept. 9: Industrial Park buildings
    - 1969 Sept.: Models of buildings, possibly Industrial Park
    - 1969 Oct. 3: Assorted projects
    - 1969 Oct. 10: Drawings, possibly matching photos of models of same date
    - 1969 Oct. 10: Two models
    - 1969 Oct. 31: Miscellaneous planning
    - 1969 Nov. 3: Industrial Park buildings and misc. planning
    - 1969 Nov. 11: Industrial Park buildings
    - 1969 Nov.: Palo Alto Square
    - 1970: Campus Topographical Maps
    - 1970: Escondido Village Drawings
    - 1970 January-March
- Additional Photographs, 2004; Accession ARCH-2004-337
  - Digital photographs (color) of the Knoll, exterior and interior, by Gerald Ratto, 2004; 2 optical disc(s) (cd-r) (136 computer files) (Box 1)
- Additional Photographs, Accession ARCH-2005-041
  - SEQ and miscellaneous photos, 1996 Sep-Dec (Box 1)
  - SEQ photos, 1997 Jan-May (Box 2)
  - SEQ photos, 1996 Feb-Sep and 1997 Jun-Oct (Box 3)
  - SEQ photos, 1997 Feb-Apr (Box 4)
  - SEQ photos, 1995 Nov, 1996 May-1997 Jan (Box 5)
  - Album -- construction photos (Box 6)
  - Album -- construction photos of model (Box 6)
  - 10 small, 5 large photos mounted on cardboard of models (Box 6)
  - Folder, large pictures -- construction of electrical engineering buildings (Box 6)
- Additional Photographs, 1995-1999; Accession ARCH-2005-300
  - Post office, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Buck Estate, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Green Library West, reconstruction, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mariposa House, exteriors, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Museum, original roof/attic, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - White Plaza (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Additional Photographs, Accession ARCH-2006-323
  - Carving "Pigott Corner" on old Engineering corner, photos by Leo Holub, contact sheets, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Carving "Pigott Corner" on old Engineering corner, photos by Leo Holub, 8 x 10 prints (3), close-up of carver at work, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carving "Pigott Corner" on old Engineering corner, photos by Leo Holub, 11 x 14 prints (4) of other images, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agassiz (Bldg.) / Hopkins Marine [prints from scanned photos including one of C.B. Van Niel's lab in April 1931] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Building 160, sandstone inventory photos [digital images on disc], 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Campus, miscellaneous photos [prints] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - General miscellaneous [prints] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Lomita Mall photos April 2002 [digital images on disc] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memorial fountain behind Memorial Church [prints], 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Museum, interior, [prints], 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Museum reconstruction [prints and negatives] (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Old Encina Gym [prints] (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Quad -- damage to balustrade and columns [prints], 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Quad miscellaneous [prints], 1994-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Quad -- seismic projects [prints and negatives] (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Houston House [slides], 1995 Oct (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Slides of assorted projects or campus locations, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Slides of assorted projects or campus locations, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Slides of assorted projects or campus locations, 1989, 1999-2000, and undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Additional Photographs, 2000; Accession ARCH-2007-075
  - Photos of the Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery prior to its renovation, 2000 June (Box 1, Item 1-3)
- Additional Photographs, Accession ARCH-2008-194
  - Board of Trustees Archive Slides
    - Board of Trustees Archive Slides-Volume 1, 6/1989-6/1991 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Board of Trustees Archive Slides-Volume 2, 9/1991-12/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
    - Board of Trustees Archive Slides-Volume 3, 6/1994-12/1997 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Board of Trustees Archive Slides-Volume 4, 1/1998-6/2001 (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
    - SEQ Progress Photos, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
    - Quad 01 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
    - Quad 01B (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
    - Quad 02 (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
    - Quad 03 (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
    - Quad 04 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Quad 05 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
    - Quad 06 (Box 3, Folder 8-11)
    - Quad 07 (Box 4, Folder 1-9)
    - Quad 08 (Box 4, Folder 10-13)
    - Quad 08 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Quad 09 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - Quad 10 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Quad 11 (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
    - Quad 12 (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    - Quad 13 (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
    - Quad 13 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Quad 14 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - Quad 90 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
    - SEQ Construction (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
    - SUMC (Box 6, Folder 8-11)
    - Scanned images for Quads 1-14 and 90; SEQ construction; SUMC, 3 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 6.3U, Box 6.2U, Box 6.1U)
    - Aerials Plans/Maps [Binder] (Box 7)
    - Planning Study (All Quads) [Binder] (Box 7)
    - Quad 1 [Binder] (Box 7)
    - Systems [Binder] (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall East Negatives [Binder] (Box 8)
    - Encina Hall South Central Negatives [Binder] (Box 8)
    - Quad 14, Quad 90 [Binder] (Box 8)
    - Quad 07-Quad 14 [Binder] (Box 8)
    - Quad 02-Quad 06 [Binder] (Box 8)
  - Additional Slides
    - Presentations (Box 9)
    - Dream Team (Box 9)
    - Sand Hill Road (Box 9)
    - Serra [Mall, Street] (Box 9)
    - SEQ (Box 9)
    - History (Box 10)
    - Aerials (Box 10)
    - Land use (Box 10)
    - Plans (land use plans by date) (Box 10)
    - Campus planning (Box 10)